Contact Information

Steven Carpenter

Full-Stack Software Developer

Email: steven.carpenter@skdevstudis.dev

Phone Number: +1 (810)-287-9252

Github: https://github.com/specCon18

Portfolio: https://scarpenter.skdevstudios.dev

Grand Blanc, Michigan

Objective Summary

I am self taught web developer, with a passion for innovating technology by designing and deploying tools that ease the development process allowing for a reliable, reproducable, experience for every user. Im currently returning to the workforce and possess current knowledge in Ansible, Svelte, Typescript, HTML, CSS, Bash scripting and Linux and a desire to design tooling that helps companies deliver their product reliably through strong interface design, modular application architechting, and reliable automation.

Work Experience

Divine Appointment Catering

Web Developer

2012-2015

- Designed and developed website for their catering business and their food truck that was being launched at the time.
- Maintained the website I designed for them until it was taken down due to slow business.

IT Manager

2015 - 2017

Service, Manage, and Maintained all IT Resources

Bitwise

Hardware Technician

2015

• Serviced and repaired hardware and network solutions for both residential and corperate clients.

Web Developer

2016-2017

• Maintained and Developed new features for several corperate clients.

Freelance IT Services

Flint Massonic Temple

2014-2019

Services:

• Serviced computers and printers when down

Nexus Fire Gaming

2014-2020

Services:

- Game Server Development
- Harware Repair
- Security Audit
- Web Development
- Educational Services

Dr. Madonna Carpenter-Jackson

2012-Present

Services:

- Security Audit
- Web Development
- Hardware Repair
- Network Management
- Device Management

Brittney Stroud

2018-Present

Services:

- Hardware Repair
- Security Audit
- Web Development
- Network Management
- Device Management
- Deployed Smart Home Environment

Personal projects

- SK Public Access Link Router
- SK Click Frontend to PALR
- YUNODOC Community Edition

Skills

Languages

- English
- Typescript
- HTML
- CSS
- Bash ### Frameworks
- Tailwind CSS
- Svelte Framework ### Tooling
- GIMP
- GIT
- Docker
- Linux
- Ansible
- Node JS ### Networking
- DNS
- Cloud Hosting

Education

Bentley Senior High School

2013-2017

Completed with a High School Diploma

GCI Certified Hardware Technician Program

2015-2016

• Completed With Comptia A+ Credential

GCI Certified Network Technician Program

2016-2017

• Completed With Comptia Network+ Credential

Activites

Hosted Game Servers for Nexus Fire Gaming

2013-2020

Learning CAD and CAM to assist in additive manufacturing

2020-present

Learning Machine Learning to work on Al Visual Recognition 2020-present

Learning Rust to write system level apps that target WASM

Jaunary 2022-Present